

Gyimah Akua Attaa Awuah

Curriculum Vitae

+84964495653



aawuah32@gmail.com



Hanoi, VN



EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree - International **Business Administration** FPT University, Hanoi, VN 2014 - 2018

St. Roses Senior High School Akwatia, GH 2008 - 2012

COURSES

160 Hours TEFL Course TEFL Fullcircle, Online 2019

LANGUAGES

English – native

Twi – native

Vietnamese – B1

Czech – A1

CHARITY

International Medical Corps -Financial support for single mothers in developing countries 2017 - 2019

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Compassionate, creative and enthusiastic teacher with valuable experience in classroom administration, professional development, and project planning. Extensive experience in the education environment as a studentcentric instructor, academic facilitator and instructional coach. Equally effective whether performing independently or as a member of a teaching team. Well versed in the technology of education, both classroom and online.

EXPERIENCE

BRITISH SCHOOL CENTER | Hanoi, VN | 7/2017 - Now

English Teacher - Full time

Teaching English students from Kindergarten to adults.

- Create a lesson plan for each weekly lecture.
- Prove one-on-one assistance to students after class.
- Motivate students to increase their passion for learning English.
- Set the topics for each class and guide the students to practice effectively.
- Develope and supervise tests and quizzes to be completed by students.
- Encourage student participation in the classroom.
- Direct students to create their own practice dialogues by using the language materials that we introduced in the classroom.

PRIVATE CLASSES | Hanoi, VN | 3/2014 - Now

English Teacher

During my studies, before I started my full time position at British School Center, I have been also working as a part time teacher at other english centers, kindergartens and as a private tutor. List of books I have been using:

- Family and friends, books 1 6
- Solution Elementary student book, books 1 9
- Grapeseed, books 1 4
- Jolly phonics
- IELTS books 1 4
- CAMBRIDGE PET, books 1 9

References Available Upon Request.